vendorseek.com 2012-12-25

# Receive Up-To 5 Free quotes for telemarketing services, fulfillment services and much more

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Service in writing to : **QuinStreet,950 Tower Lane,6th floor,Foster City,CA 94404** OR via our Contact Us form on our website.

**Privacy Policy**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please see our contact details at the end of this document.

**Your privacy is our main concern.**

The following privacy policy details how we gather information, how that information is shared, and what practices VendorSeek.com implements to ensure your information is safe and protected. 

Use of www.VendorSeek.com (the "Website") to receive quotes or to register as a Vendor in our Approved Vendor Network indicates your agreement with this privacy policy

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that VendorSeek.com does not own or control, or to people who VendorSeek.com does not employ. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California has passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customers personal information (as defined by the act) to any third party for direct marketing purposes to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information.

If you are a California resident you may request this information from VendorSeek.com or any of its affiliates by completing our Contact Us form or you may send us correspondence at the following address: QuinStreet,950 Tower Lane,6th floor,Foster City,CA 94404. VendorSeek.com is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from a customer per calendar year.

**What information does VendorSeek.com gather?**

 _Personally Identifiable Information:_

When you use our Website to receive free quotes for products or services (a “Quote Seeker”) or to receive referrals of Quote Seekers for your products or services (a “Vendor”), you will be required to disclose certain personal information to us.

 _Quote Seekers:_

As a Quote Seeker you need only provide the following information:

1\. Answer a few qualifying questions specific to the product or service for which you are seeking quotes.  
2\. Provide basic contact information including: Name, Company Name, Position, Address, Phone Number, Email Address, and Website.

 _Vendors:_

As an approved Vendor, you will have the opportunity to register on the Website and receive referrals of Quote Seekers who require the products or services that you offer. To register as a Vendor, you need only provide the following information:

1\. Provide general contact information including: Name, Company Name, Address, Phone Number, Email Address(es), and Website.  
2\. Select the categories for which you wish to receive referrals and provide specific parameters as to the types of referrals you wish to receive. Note: these parameters must be in accordance with the information that is being gathered from Quote Seekers through the request forms on the Website.  
3\. Upon registration, the Vendor must also provide a valid credit card to be utilized for all billing activity.

Note: Registration as a Vendor is subject to the VendorSeek approval process.

VendorSeek.com will keep the identity of Vendors in our Approved Vendor Network confidential, unless the Vendor should choose to utilize any of the advertising opportunities that are offered by VendorSeek.com that would identify the Vendor as a member of our Approved Vendor Network. This would include, but not be limited to: logo ads, instant intros, newsletter ads, industry experts articles, and testimonials authorized for use on the Website.

 _Non-Personally Identifiable Information:_

While visiting the Website individuals can view pages and need not worry about revealing personally identifiable information. VendorSeek.com collects various types of non-personally identifiable information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies or other Internet tracking technologies.

_Cookies:_

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Website. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Website. We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You may remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers "help" file. 

Cookies are stored only if you select to save your password on the login screen. A cookie is created so that we are able to retrieve your settings. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you dont have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by www.VendorSeek.com only. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies. You may disable or reject cookies if your browser permits. Please be advised that this may prevent you from accessing certain features of VendorSeek.com. Having trouble while cookies is disabled? Contact our Customer Service department via our Contact Us form

_Log Files:_

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically from your browser or Internet session and store it in log files. This information includes your Internet protocol (IP) address, the browser type that you are using, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit URLs, the operating system on your computer, date/time stamp, and click stream data. 

We use this non-personally identifiable information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. 

We also engage third-party tracking service providers that use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Website. 

**Use of Information:**

VendorSeek.com gathers information in an attempt to introduce business-to-business vendors to consumers in order to satisfy their professional needs. 

If you elect to provide us with personal information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from VendorSeek.com and from our clients. Once you sign up as a Quote Seeker, you will automatically be added to our email distribution list and will begin receiving additional information such as newsletters, updates and other publications. In addition, your personal information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other VendorSeek.com sales and marketing efforts.

The non-personally identifiable information that we collect is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

**Ownership of Quote Seeker Information:**

As the purpose of VendorSeek.com is to match Quote Seekers with pre-approved Vendors, information submitted for the purpose of receiving free quotes will be owned by VendorSeek.com and will also become the property of the Vendors in our Approved Vendor Network who are referred to the Quote Seeker. By placing a request to receive free quotes, the Quote Seeker accepts this use of their information.

**Links to other sites:**

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by VendorSeek.com. Please be aware that VendorSeek.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website, to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Website. 

**Information sharing policy- Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):**

There are instances in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

_Non-personally identifiable information:_

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third party partners of VendorSeek.com on an anonymous basis.

We also share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our customers. This information does not identify individual users. VendorSeek.com will refer business related information in leads to interested parties. VendorSeek.com never sells or releases company information to other parties unless it is directly related to matching a request to the Vendors in our Approved Vendor Network.

 _Agents:_

VendorSeek.com processes payments due from its Vendors through a leading merchant account provider that upholds the highest security standards available. This company does not share or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

 _Service Providers:_

VendorSeek.com is considered a "third-party referral service." We use other third parties (or Vendors) to provide business-related services on our Website. When you sign up to VendorSeek.com we will share business-related (non-proprietary) information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

 _Legally required disclosures:_

VendorSeek.com reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and to comply with judicial proceedings, court order or legal processes served on the Website. 

_Business Transitions:_

In the event that VendorSeek.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. 

**Security:**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Website, please complete our Contact Us form and we will respond.

**Information on circulation:**

Once signed up with VendorSeek.com and subject to you having opted in to receiving additional circulations, you may receive additional publications such as newsletters and e-mails that contain content regarding the Website, content changes and special promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present you with the option of not receiving these types of communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-Out” below. 

**Ordering services:**

In order for VendorSeek.com to service you properly, you will need to provide us with company-specific information. Both vendors and those submitting requests are required to complete an online form which requests specific data. This includes contact information, demographics and information designed to assist you with searching for specific vendor/request-related inquiries. Various departments at VendorSeek.com may review your companys information. Credit card information is stored securely through encryption and SSL connection. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

**Access - changing information:**

Vendors with VendorSeek.com can change profile information at any time by accessing their profiles with the appropriate sign-in name and password. Individuals who place requests can update, change or remove information by filling out our Contact Us form on our website. 

**Choice/Opt Out:**

 _Personally Identifiable Information – Opting out:_

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications or other additional marketing material, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or other marketing material or by filling out our Contact Us form on our website.

 _Non-Personally Identifiable Information – Opting out:_

As noted above, our Website collects non-personally identifiable information about your website activities using cookies and other tracking devices. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting the Website.

**Childrens Privacy**

In compliance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), VendorSeek.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

**Changes to privacy policy:**

By using this Website, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy, as may be amended from time to time, and to VendorSeek.coms processing of personal information for the purposes given above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that those changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our Website for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

**Model Disclosure:** VendorSeek.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Website www.VendorSeek.com. Because VendorSeek.com wishes to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

**Contact Details:** : If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first complete our Contact Us form or you may send us correspondence at the following address: QuinStreet,950 Tower Lane,6th floor,Foster City,CA 94404. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> where you may submit a complaint. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.
